consumerautosource.com 2016-04-29

# ConsumerAutoSource.com Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy:

At ConsumerAutoSource.com, your privacy is a top priority, and we are committed to protecting your privacy both on ConsumerAutoSource.com and online. This Privacy Policy provides details on how we treat any personal information you may submit to us.

This Privacy Policy applies to this website, ConsumerAutoSource.com (the “Site”). Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to the information collected through the Site and not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link.

#### Information We Collect and Use

We will collect and use personal information about you to respond to your request for products and services offered through the Site. Specifically, we collect information provided by you in connection with obtaining quotes for insurance products and services. For example, you will be asked to provide your full name, address, telephone number, email, information about your automobile(s), and other information in order to be matched to insurance carriers and agents who may provide you a quote for their insurance services based upon the profile of information you provide.

We also collect demographic information. Demographic information is all other information such as gender, zip code, or any information that is not tied to your personal information. In addition, we might receive information about you from other online or offline sources and may add that information to your existing account.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We share personal information about you under the following circumstances:

Insurance Quote Request - If you submit a request on the Site for quotes for insurance products or services, we will share the personal information contained in your request form (such as your full name, address, telephone number, email, information about your cars, etc.) with third parties, which include insurance agents, insurance carriers, lead aggregators, and other insurance service providers (“Service Providers”) in our network to process and fulfill your request for insurance quotes. In some circumstances, we may obtain additional information about you and/or share that information with Service Providers in our network.

All Service Providers in our network have entered into agreements with us, and are required to comply with federal and state privacy regulations. By submitting your request to us, you understand that Service Providers may contact you by telephone (on a recorded line), automated calling, email, or regular mail based on the information you provided to us in order to process and fulfill your request, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission, any state equivalent Do Not Call List, or the Do Not Call List of an internal company. If one of the Service Providers contacts you and you wish not to be contacted again by that Service Provider with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that Service Provider not to contact you again. Please note that the Service Providers may maintain the information you provided whether you elect to use their services.

Aggregate, Non-Personal, or De-identified Information. We may share aggregated information (i.e., information about you and other users collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you) and other non-personal, de-identified, or anonymous information we collect with third parties, including affiliates to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our Site and on the websites of third parties.

As Required by Law. We may be required to share your personal information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

Business Transfer. As with any other business, it is possible that we, in the future could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by us, including your personal information, customer and business account information, but would continue to be bound by this policy unless you consent otherwise.

#### Cookies and IP Addresses

To serve you faster and with better quality, we use "cookies" technology. Cookies are small bits of code, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive, which enable a Website to "personalize" itself for each user. We generally use cookies to reduce the time it takes for pages to load on your computer and to assist with customer tracking. Customer tracking (or "click-stream") data collected by us is used to optimize your experience by learning whether or not you successfully used the Site. Additionally, we may capture click-stream data on some of our partner's websites, limited to the activity involved with the completion of offers listed on our website. This information is used to monitor the performance of our partners. We also may use cookies to deliver targeted advertising on our website, websites owned by our sister companies, or websites of third parties.

We also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

#### Clear Gifs

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movement of Web users. Clear gifs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information. We also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails the recipients have opened. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

#### Emails

You may register to receive communications from us directly on our website or through a third party. Upon registering, we will periodically send you newsletters and other e-mails with offers and promotions. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by sending an email to ConsumerAutoSource.com Customer Care at info@ConsumerAutoSource.com. (You may also opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails).

Third Party Advertisers. Please note that we can only control its own mailing list and policies. Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and you may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their email communications.

#### Confidentiality and Security

The security of your personal information is very important, and we take a number of steps to safeguard it. For example, we limit access to personal information to those employees or agents who assist us in providing requested products and services to you and maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard personal information about you.

#### Third Party Links

This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide on the Site. However, when you visit websites to which ConsumerAutoSource.com links, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policy. If you choose to obtain certain services through a third party site, the data collected by the third party is governed by that third party's privacy policy. A third party site will also have its own policy regarding the use of cookies and clear gifs. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

#### A Special Note about Children's Privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to use this website. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you can use the services offered on our website only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. Please see our Terms of Use for more information.

#### Removing Your Information

Federal and state regulations require that we maintain all information (including your personal information) submitted through the Site for various time periods. In order to comply with these regulations, we cannot delete your information from our database.

#### Questions and Suggestions

If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by sending an email to: [info@ConsumerAutoSource.com](mailto:info@ConsumerAutoSource.com)

#### Your Consent

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

#### California User Consumer Rights

California User Consumer Rights. In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](http://www.dca@dca.ca.gov/). For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy or in how we will use your personal information, we will post such changes here. You will be notified if any of the material changes that affect the use of your personal information and asked to opt-in to the new use of your personal information. If you do not agree with the changes to how your information will be used, please do not continue to use this website.

By using the Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use any of the Site. When you request insurance quotes or other information through the Site, you are authorizing us to share information with our business partners, who may contact you by phone, email, or mail. If you do not want further communication from them, please notify the partner directly. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our website to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our Privacy Policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Policy.

**Updated January 20, 2012**
